http://www.reigatemethodist.org.uk/new-here40210/privacy-policy/

Search
Reigate Methodist Church
HomeNew Here?Who we areKey PeopleWeddings and BaptismsHistoryFAQsReigate Community CentreContact UsFind UsMethodismPrivacy PolicycoronavirusLearning & GrowingTaketime TogetherHouse GroupsCoursesActivities & EventsWhat's OnChildren & Young PeopleSeniorsSocial ActivitiesMusic & DramaWorshipSunday ServiceYouthChildrenMessy Church
Home > New Here?
> Privacy Policy
New Here?Who we areWeddings and BaptismsHistoryFAQsReigate Community CentreContact UsFind UsMethodismPrivacy Policycoronavirus
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting personal information and respecting people's rights as to how their information is handled. Reigate Methodist Church is compliant with the GDPR which came into effect in May 2018.
Personal data is only used for the purpose for which it has been collected
Individuals always opt in to providing their data and agreeing how it is used
No data kept by the Church is used for marketing or fundraising purposes
No data is passed on to other organisations, expect where the Church is legally required to do so
We follow the data protection procedures stipulated by the Methodist Church in the UK, and the full privacy notice is available at https://www.tmcp.org.uk/about/data-protection/managing-trustees-privacy-notice
Cookies are used on this website only for the purpose of recording the number of visitors, as we don't use it to collect personal information.
Our Data Controller is Jacqui Waters and she will respond if you wish to make a ‘subject data access request’.  She can be contacted via the Community Centre office on 01737 652256.
Reigate Methodist is a registered charity (no. 1127082). This church website is powered by Church Edit
